wenworld.com 2000-10-09

# Wenatchee World Online Copyright notice

**Local news**  

**Recreation**  

**A & E**  

**Community**  

**Classifieds**  

**WebCams**  

**Hobbies & Fun**  

**Contact Us**  

**Our Partners**  

| 

The Wenatchee World, publisher of The World Online, has a firm commitment to privacy. We take your privacy concerns seriously and want to make every effort to address those concerns. That is why we have adopted the following policy on information gathering and disclosure.

* * *

**Your Personal Information**

> From time to time, we will ask for information that personally identifies you, as in our user surveys or registration for The Wenatchee World services such as e-mail, forums, or promotions. We use this information to operate The Wenatchee World's services, provide you with the highest quality services and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest.
> 
> We will not disclose any personal information without your advance permission except when we believe the law requires us to do so or the disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or property of The Wenatchee World, or as explained below or in our User Agreement.
> 
> In order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and others, we may disclose user information but only in a form that does not identify individual users. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are male or within a certain age range.
> 
> Occasionally, we may disclose personal information in other circumstances, but we will only do this if we have explained at the time we collect the information the purpose for which it will be disclosed.

* * *

 **Children's Privacy**

> The Wenatchee World is particularly concerned with providing a safe online environment for children. The Wenatchee World strongly recommends parental supervision when a child uses the Internet, and particularly when a child enters a forum or uses e-mail.
> 
> We also encourage parents to instruct their children not to give out personal information in these areas. A number of commercial products are available to help limit your child's access to material on the Internet that you may consider harmful or inappropriate.
> 
> Other services and information providers accessible through The World Online have their own policies about children's privacy and you should contact them directly for their policies.

* * *

**Electronic Commerce**

> The Wenatchee World may host online stores that sell a variety of goods and services. These stores may collect information from you such as your name, credit card number and other contact information. The Wenatchee World does not collect, use or disclose this information nor does it own or control the stores or have responsibility for transactions made by those merchants. If you would like to know more about the information collected when you participate in electronic commerce on or through this site, please contact the store merchants directly.

* * *

**Cookies**

> A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows The World Online to recognize you each time you visit the site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information. Instead, they allow us to see which parts of our site you have used so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. Cookies may be used to provide you with information and special opportunities tailored to your interests.

* * *

**Direct Mailings and "Opting Out"**

> We may send you information about various products and services. If you don't want to receive this information, you can "opt out" by sending us an e-mail to [webmaster@wenworld.com](mailto:webmaster@wenworld.com) and requesting that you not receive any of these offers.

* * *

 **You Can Change Your Private Information at any Time**

> We may store information you provide to The Wenatchee World for an indefinite time. However, please feel free to change, update or delete this information at any time by sending an e-mail [webmaster@wenworld.com](mailto:webmaster@wenworld.com).

* * *

**Remember the risks whenever you use the Internet**

> You should know that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on The World Online (for example, in forums), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to The World Online and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, our partners and other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through The World Online have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

* * *

 **Tell Us How We're Doing**

> If you have any questions or comments about our policies, please contact us by sending an e-mail to [webmaster@wenworld.com](mailto:webmaster@wenworld.com).

|   |   |   | 

**Wenatchee World online forms**  

* * *

* * *

* * *

**[Online banner  
ad rates](http://www.wenworld.com/Contactus/adrates.html)**

---|---|---|---|---  

* * *

[Movies](http://www.wenworld.com/arts/movies/index.html) | [WebCams](http://www.wenworld.com/WebCam/WebCam.html) | [Kid's Stuff](http://hbz.wenworld.com/) | [Contact Us](http://www.wenworld.com/contactus/staff.html) | [Homefinder](http://www.wenworld.com/homefinder/hf.html) © [Copyright](http://www.wenworld.com/Contactus/copyright.html) 2000 The Wenatchee World  
P.O. Box 1511, Wenatchee, WA 98807-1511  
Send [comments](http://www.wenworld.com/contactus/Comment.html) or questions about www.wenworld.com to the [webmaster](mailto:webmaster@wenworld.com)
